<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AxClass xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Name>CashManagementFlights</Name>
	<SourceCode>
		<Declaration><![CDATA[
/// <summary>
/// The <c>CashManagementFlights</c> class provides a centralized location for flights related to Cash Management functionality.
/// </summary>
internal final static class CashManagementFlights
{
    // This flight reduces deadlocks during processing of customer transactions by isolating each thread with a separate SpecContext buffer.
    // Created 10.0.4
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Once a strategy is in place to enable functionality for all customers
    internal static const str EnableCustTransSettleTransactionFlight = 'EnableCustTransSettleTransaction';

    // This flight provides regression protection for the Pds datasource on the CustOpenTrans form.
    // The datasource has been disabled by default to remove a self-join on the form query table CustTransOpen as a performance optimization.
    // Created 10.0.14
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Once all customers adopt 10.0.14 with no issues. Once removed, the Pds datasource should be disabled permanently.
    internal static const str CustOpenTransFormReenableObsoletePdsDatasourceFlight = 'CustOpenTransFormReenableObsoletePdsDatasource';

    // This flight provides regression protection for the change in behavior to the SpecTransManager::construct() method
    // Created 10.0.16
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Once all customers adopt 10.0.16 with no issues. Once removed, conditions should be adjusted to remove flighting cases.
    internal static const str SpecTransAllowCacheInBatchProcessingFlight = 'SpecTransAllowCacheInBatchProcessingFlight';

    /// This flight provides the ability to turn off the cash flow generation document single transaction functionality.
    /// Created 10.0.18
    /// Default state: Off
    /// Remove: Once all customer adopt 10.0.18 with no issues.
    internal static const str LedgerCovDocumentSingleTransactionScopeKillSwitchFlight = 'LedgerCovDocumentSingleTransactionScopeKillSwitch';
}
]]></Declaration>
		<Methods />
	</SourceCode>
</AxClass>