<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AxClass xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Name>LocalizationFlights</Name>
	<SourceCode>
		<Declaration><![CDATA[
internal final static class LocalizationFlights
{
    // This flight allows to use reverse order for CFDI relations when performing validation before document cancellation.
    // Created 10.0.20
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Once a strategy is in place to enable functionality for all customers
    internal static const SysFlightName eInvoiceCFDIUseReverseReferenceOrder = 'eInvoiceCFDIUseReverseReferenceOrder';

    // This flight allows to ignore the changes made in KB4617956.
    // Created 10.0.21
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: When version 10.0.21 becomes globally available.
    internal const SysFlightName IgnoreChangesMadeInKB4617956ReceiptReport_TH = 'IgnoreChangesMadeInKB4617956ReceiptReport_TH';

    // This flight provides regression protection for the SAD documents with multiple positions and invoices posting.
    // Created 10.0.20
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Once all customers adopt 10.0.20 with no issues. Once removed, conditions should be adjusted to remove flighting cases.
    internal static const SysFlightName SADDocumentsWithMultipleInvoicesPosting = 'SADDocumentsWithMultipleInvoicesPosting';

    // This flight allows controlling print management destinations via Use print managmement destinations flag on posting/printing forms.
    // Created 10.0.20
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Once PEAP testing concludes.
    internal static const SysFlightName ForcePrintJobSettings = 'ForcePrintJobSettings';

    // This flight reverts due date rounding logic for Japan to increment month if cutoff day is bigger than calculated due date day of month.
    // Created 10.0.20
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Once we make sure that there is no customer in Japan that need old processing logic or we implement customer accessible switch.
    internal const SysFlightName paymDayUseConsolidatedCountryRegionDateRounding_JP = 'paymDayUseConsolidatedCountryRegionDateRounding_JP';

    // This flight allows to ignore the call to the checkPurchQty method for Russian localization for specific customers.
    // Created 10.0.21
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Never
    internal const SysFlightName IgnoreCallCheckPurchQty_RU = 'IgnoreCallCheckPurchQty_RU';

    // This flight reverts the sales invoice amount calculation for EE VAT Declaration back to using order subtotal instead of the formula "invoice total - sales tax".
    // Created 10.0.21
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Once we make sure that the formula for sales invoice amount is correct and the change doesn't break something
    internal const SysFlightName EEVATDeclaration_UseSalesBalanceForSalesInvoiceInvoiceAmount = 'EEVATDeclaration_UseSalesBalanceForSalesInvoiceInvoiceAmount';

    // This flight reverts tax withhold transactions filtering in PND3 and PND53 reports back to "NoExistsJoin PND2" condition.
    // Created 10.0.21
    // Default state: Off
    // Remove: Once all customers adopt 10.0.21 with no issues.
    internal const SysFlightName TaxWithholdPND_UseNoExistsPND2ForFiltering = 'TaxWithholdPND_UseNoExistsPND2ForFiltering';
}
]]></Declaration>
		<Methods />
	</SourceCode>
</AxClass>