<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AxClass xmlns:i="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Name>TradeCustomizationsEventHandler</Name>
	<SourceCode>
		<Declaration><![CDATA[
/// <summary>
/// The <c>TradeCustomizationsEventHandler</c> class is the container class that has the customization
/// methods that are called from forms in the higher level layers.There is no code that is expected in
/// the SYS layer. Partners and customers who want to customize the business logic must create
/// additional classes that contain the customization logic, and attach those additional class methods
/// as post event handlers to the customization methods in this class.It is important for methods in
/// the additional classes to examine the existence of a relevant configuration key and if the
/// configuration key is not present, the methods will not perform any action.
/// </summary>
public class TradeCustomizationsEventHandler
{
}
]]></Declaration>
		<Methods>
			<Method>
				<Name>purchParmLineActive</Name>
				<Source><![CDATA[
    /// <summary>
    /// Enables the customization of the <c>Active</c> method of the <c>PurchParmLine</c> data source in
    /// the <c>PurchEditLines</c> form in the higher layers.
    /// </summary>
    /// <param name="_formDataSource">
    /// The form data source that corresponds to the <c>PurchParmLine</c> table in the <c>PurchEditLine</c>
    /// form.
    /// </param>
    /// <remarks>
    /// No code is expected in the SYS layer.
    /// </remarks>
    public static void purchParmLineActive(FormDataSource _formDataSource)
    {
    }

]]></Source>
			</Method>
			<Method>
				<Name>salesLineLinkActive</Name>
				<Source><![CDATA[
    /// <summary>
    /// Enables the customization of the <c>linkActive</c> method in the <c>SalesLine</c> data source of
    /// the <c>SalesLine</c> form EMCKDHB24in higher layers.
    /// </summary>
    /// <param name="_formSalesLine">
    /// The form data source that corresponds to the table from which the <c>SalesLine</c> form is called.
    /// </param>
    public static void salesLineLinkActive(FormDataSource _formSalesLine)
    {
    }

]]></Source>
			</Method>
		</Methods>
	</SourceCode>
</AxClass>